Make 4 different Pages ata kama ni static....

Image called lamborghini logo ndio the header image kwa home page na ya website

Lamborghini 101 //home//
---------------
Automobili Lamborghini S.p.A. (Italian: [lamborˈɡiːni] ( listen)) is an Italian brand and manufacturer of luxury sports cars and SUVs based in Sant'Agata Bolognese, Italy. The company is owned by the Volkswagen Group through its subsidiary Audi.

//image 1//

Ferruccio Lamborghini, an Italian manufacturing magnate, founded Automobili Ferruccio Lamborghini S.p.A. in 1963 to compete with established marques, including Ferrari. The company gained wide acclaim in 1966 for the Miura sports coupé, which established rear mid-engine, rear wheel drive as the standard layout for high-performance cars of the era. Lamborghini grew rapidly during its first decade, but sales plunged in the wake of the 1973 worldwide financial downturn and the oil crisis. The firm's ownership changed three times after 1973, including a bankruptcy in 1978. American Chrysler Corporation took control of Lamborghini in 1987 and sold it to Malaysian investment group Mycom Setdco and Indonesian group V'Power Corporation in 1994. In 1998, Mycom Setdco and V'Power sold Lamborghini to the Volkswagen Group where it was placed under the control of the group's Audi division.

//image 2//

New products and model lines were introduced to the brand's portfolio and brought to the market and saw an increased productivity for the brand Lamborghini. In the late 2000s, during the worldwide financial crisis and the subsequent economic crisis, Lamborghini's sales saw a drop of nearly 50 percent.

//image 3//

Lamborghini produces sports cars and V12 engines for offshore powerboat racing. Lamborghini currently produces the V12-powered Aventador and the V10-powered Huracán.

//image 4//

P1
-Murcielago.
--------------

The Lamborghini Murciélago is a supercar produced by Italian automaker Lamborghini between 2001 and 2010. Successor to the Diablo and flagship of the automaker's lineup, the Murciélago was introduced as a coupé in 2001. The Murcielago was first available in North America for the 2002 model year. The automaker's first new design in eleven years, the car was also the brand's first new model under the ownership of German parent company Audi, which is owned by Volkswagen. It is styled by Peruvian-born Belgian Luc Donckerwolke, Lamborghini's head of design from 1998 to 2005.

A roadster version was introduced in 2004, followed by the updated LP 640 coupé and roadster and limited edition LP 650–4 Roadster. The final variation to wear the Murciélago nameplate was the LP 670–4 SuperVeloce, powered by the largest and final evolution of the Lamborghini V12 engine. Production of the Murciélago ended on November 5, 2010, with a total run of 4,099 cars. Its successor, the Aventador, was released at the 2011 Geneva Motor Show.

-Gallardo.
--------------
The Lamborghini Gallardo (/ɡaɪˈjɑːrdoʊ/; Italian: [ɡaʎˈʎardo]) is a sports car built by Lamborghini from 2003 to 2013. It is Lamborghini's best-selling model with 14,022 being built throughout its lifetime. Named after a famous breed of fighting bull, the V-10 Gallardo has been Lamborghini's sales leader and stable-mate to a succession of V-12 flagship models—first to the Lamborghini Murciélago (4,099 built between 2001 and 2011), then to the current flagship Lamborghini Aventador. On November 25, 2013, the last Gallardo was rolled off the production line.

Production of the replacement for the Gallardo, the Huracán, began in 2014.

p2-Huracan.
--------------

The Lamborghini Huracán is the perfect fusion of technology and design. With its crisp, streamlined lines, designed to cut through the air and tame the road, you'll get a thrill just by looking at it. The only thing better than taking in this beauty from a distance is actually touching it. The finest Italian craftsmanship lavished on finishes of unprecedented prestige and quality. Your heart will leap when you sit inside and press the ignition button, feeling what it means to have a naturally aspirated V10 engine behind you, and all the technology you need to control it right at your fingertips. Your eyes will enthrall you a final time once you take in the full-LED lighting system and the 12.3" TFT instrument panel, which provides an unrivalled driving experience.

Sculptured and sensual, the Huracán’s design is based on the spiky hexagonal forms of the carbon atom, while the seamless roof profile is an unmistakable mark of the Lamborghini DNA. The Huracán is unique even in the dark, thanks to the alluringly “technological” light of its full-LED lighting system.

-Aventador.
--------------
The new Aventador models have been designed to exceed the concept of performance itself, establishing a new benchmark for super sports cars, and turning the cars of the future into a present-day reality. A supercar family that has already become a legend in its own right.

A Lamborghini must always be recognizable at first sight. This is why each detail of the Aventador models embodies at best the DNA of the iconic Lamborghini look: the authentic design masterpieces together stark dynamism with aggression to produce a cutting edge carbon fiber monocoque. The interior of the Aventador combines high-level technology and luxury equipment with premium-quality materials, skilfully crafted with the expertise characteristic of the finest Italian traditions. 

p5-Special Editions //both on one page//
-----------------------------------
+1. Veneno

The Lamborghini Veneno Roadster takes the aerodynamic efficiency of a racing prototype onto everyday roads. This super sports car is characterized by optimal aerodynamics in order to guarantee stability in fast curves and a behavior like a racing prototype. All of this on a car devised for the road. The perfect car for sports-driving lovers.

With a 6.5 liter aspirated V12 engine and a top speed of 355 km/h, this Lamborghini concept car represents state-of-the-art design inspired by aeronautics, capable of giving you the indescribable feeling of flying on the road. Faithful to the Lamborghini lines, the Veneno is characterized by extreme proportions, emerging in the forceful arrow-shaped front as well as alternating razor-sharp lines and sleek, tight surfaces.

+2. Centenario

The new Lamborghini Centenario represents a new, extremely precious piece in Lamborghini's one-off strategy. It is a perfect example of the innovative design and the engineering skills of the bull-branded manufacturer.
The best tribute to the 100th anniversary of the birth of Mr. Ferruccio Lamborghini, a man who managed to create a world-class brand, and who always believed that nothing is impossible, thus producing legendary and extraordinary vehicles that made history for super sports cars.
The Centenario is an homage to this visionary man and to the future he believed so much in. And we at Lamborghini still believe in that future. Find out more: from the performance to the dimensions to the unique characteristics to the detailed technical specifications of the Lamborghini Centenario.

Equipped with a 770 CV aspirated V12 engine springing from 0 to 100 km/h in 2.8 seconds, the newly-born Lamborghini car has been produced in a limited edition, for a total of 40 models: 20 Coupés and 20 Roadsters will be delivered to Lamborghini collectors and fans starting from 2017.
The Centenario has been conceived with the purpose of exploring new technological and design opportunities, to look at the future through the lens of innovation. One of the most exclusive (and sought-after) cars in the whole world.


//ingiza images respectiely to the name of image//